http://www.leopoldgallery.com/privacy-policy/

0
item
items
0
MenuArtistsWind SculpturesLyman Whitaker Wind SculpturesGifts of RemembranceExhibitionsHappy Customers CloseArt ProjectsArt ProjectsKC Royals ArtFrontline Heroes CloseAbout UsContactTour the GalleryTestimonial VideosLeopold FoundationPeopleNews & VideosPaul’s BookExhibitionsGallery Blog CloseKC Chiefs ArtArt Consulting
816.333.3111
EMAIL US
Privacy Policy
LEOPOLDgallery and ARTconsulting operates https://www.leopoldgallery.com/ This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name.
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our site https://www.leopoldgallery.com/. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data. The Log Data section is for businesses that use analytics or tracking services in websites or apps, like Google Analytics. For the full disclosure section.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with monthly newsletters, from which you can unsubscribe at any time.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Third Party Advertising and Tracking
We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here (Link to TRUSTe global opt-out: http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of 3/2/16 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
LEOPOLDgallery and ARTconsulting
324 W. 63rd St.
Kansas City, MO 64113
816.333.3111
info@leopoldgallery.com
www.leopoldgallery.com
Art Search
Art Search
Site Search
Site Search
Recent NewsMeet the Artist Series: Nancy TeagueNovember 18, 2020Paul’s Audition for Survivor. You’ll Love It.August 25, 2020Meet the Artist Series: Elizabeth WashburnMay 11, 2020Meet the Artist Series: Louis CoptApril 24, 2020Meet the Artist Series: Jenny KrugerMarch 30, 2020Meet the Artist Series: MJ RigbyMarch 23, 2020Lyman Whitaker Wind Sculpture Exhibit at Dallas ArboretumFebruary 23, 2020Jacob Burmood Sculpture Dedicated at Arrowhead Stadium, KC Studio MagazineJanuary 19, 2020
Artists
Wind Sculptures
Art Projects
Contact
Art Blog
Exhibitions
ArtistsGary Bowling, Mark Brasuell, Jacob Burmood, Mark Cook, Louis Copt, Phil Epp, Carol Fleming, Linda Ganstrom, Thomas Gieseke, Addison Hanna, Drew Hine, Wind Spinners, Tyler Kimball, Christina Klein, Jenny Kruger, Kinetic Sculptures, William Lobdell, Mike McMullen, Jerry Moon,  Michael Moran, Lori Norwood, Ed Pennebaker, Charles Porter, Dave Regier, Regier Sculpture, Ken & Tina Riesterer, MJ Rigby, William Rose, Kyle Stanley, NCECA Exhibition, Nancy Teague, Brad Teare,  Elizabeth Washburn, Gary Wilks, Lyman Whitaker Wind Sculptures.
From the BlogMeet the Artist Series: Nancy TeagueNovember 18, 2020Paul’s Audition for Survivor. You’ll Love It.August 25, 2020Meet the Artist Series: Elizabeth WashburnMay 11, 2020
QuicklinksArt Search
Art Projects
News & Videos
Lyman Whitaker Wind Spinner Sculptures
Art Blog
LEAVE GOOGLE REVIEW
Follow us!
Join Our Mailing List
Thanks for signing up!
Email Address
Sign Up
By submitting this form, you are granting: Leopold Gallery, 324 W63rd St, Kansas City, Missouri, 64113, United States, https://www.leopoldgallery.com permission to email you. You may unsubscribe via the link found at the bottom of every email.
(See our Email Privacy Policy for details.) Emails are serviced by Constant Contact.
